Benjamin Franklin Papers Part 13 -- Miscellaneous Franklin Materials 1640-1791 Mss.B.F85inventory13
American Philosophical Society
- Miscellaneous Franklin Materials
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 7p.; Draft of Divorce Laws and the Division of the Children
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 12p.; A Discussion on the Advantages of Free Trade
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 4p.; On the Advantages of Paper Money
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 2p.; Plan for the Adjustment of the Tobacco Trade
    Between the Colonists in America and the company.
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 2p.; Calculation of Interest on Money
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; Correction of a Form of Passport for a Ship
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 2p.; Names of the Americans who Stole their Advance Payments from the Vessel "Le Marquis de la Fayette."
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; Scheme for Making Rivers Navigable
    Redeeming swamps and marshes towards New Orleans.
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Maps of Governor Franklin's Lands on the Rancocus Creek
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Designs for an Emblem of the Thirteen Original States
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 4p.; Catalogue of Latin and Swedish Books
    Concerning Oddities of Electricity, 1757; German Version of Dr. Franklin's Letter, Leipsic, 1758, 8 vo.; Concerning Electrical Charges, Glass and Porcelain, Kongl. Svenska Vetenskaps Akad. (Stockholm) Handlingar, XIX, 1758; Opinions of Physicists, Ibid., XX, 1759; Contrary Electricities with Charges, Ibid., XXIII; Electrical Experiments with Phosphorus, Ibid., XXIV, 1763; Histories, Journals and Experiments, Ibid., XXVII and XXIX, 1766 and 1768; Electrical Experiments, Melting of Metals, Ibid., XXX, 1769; Notes made in Stockholm, Ibid., XXXI, 1770; Investigation of a Perpetual Electrophore, New Light on Electric Theories. Ibid., XXXVIII, 1777, etc.
    (In German.)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, A. Diss. 61p.; Reyhermann's "Never Ceasing Source of Gold."
    Dedication and introduction. (Referred to in LIX, 14-18 and 21, see Vol. II, p. 235.)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, A. Mem. 2p.; Genealogical Record of the Hartung Family from 1589 to 1777
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 8p.; Description of an Ingenious Planetary System; of a very fine Turner's Lathe; of Baron Ludwig von Holberg's Comparative History of Oriental and Indian Heroes, in the Manner of Plutarch
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 2p.; List of Men who left America on the Brigantine "Rising States."
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; List of Prize Crew on the Ship "John and Thomas" and List of Men taken Prisoners on the Prize Ship "Grace."
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; Statistics of Population, etc., in Nantucket, 1786
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; List of Latin Classic Works about to be Published
    With Prices.
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; List of French Officers and Men Taken Prisoners while Serving in the United States
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; List of British Troops Forming an Expedition under Gen Sir Henry Clinton
    Supposed to be directed against Philadelphia.
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Report on the Commerce of Saxony with Foreign Countries
    Possibilities of trade with the United States.
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 9p.; Bill of Expenses for the Duke de Lyancourt
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 3p.; List of Tenants in Ireland, with Their Holdings, etc
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; Request to Congress to Allow Baron d'Anterroches to Return to France
    A French soldier in the English army.
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 2p.; List of Stores on Board the Privateer "Dolphin."
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 3p.; Inventory of a Vessel for Sale
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 6p.; Estimate of the Cost of a Soldier's Outfit
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 2p.; List of Clothing to be Imported for the Navy
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; Location and Extent of John Williams's Land in Bucks County (Pa.)
  - Plan of a Tract of Land Belonging to Lawrence Growden and Langhorne Biles, in Bucks County, Pa., 1743 November 11; 1 map, 31.7 x 20.3 cm; Mem. 1p.; Scull, Nicholas, 1686?-1761?
    Other Finding Aids note
    Realms of Gold, 15 (2).
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 4p.; Recruits and Supplies Furnished to the Continental Army at Three Rivers, in 1776
    (Copy. In triplicate.)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, D. 1p.; Form of Passport Given by the French Government
    To individuals, in certain cases.
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Mem. 1p.; A Statement of Joseph Ormston's Shares of Proprieties in New Jersey
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Table. 1p.; Logographe Française
  - to WTF, 1783 April 20; A.L.S. 1p.; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
    Will see him in a day or two; sends some late American papers.
  - To [Richard] Bache, c. 1783; Dr. of L 2 p.; Franklin, Benjamin
    Introducing the Messrs. Perrin who ae going to America with a view of carrying on from thence commercial connection with France.